<topics>
	
<topic>
<number>51</number>
<title>Do we need sex education in schools?</title>
<description>
An adult user now has a partner for the first time and searched the Internet for information on contraception. They found that some schools provide sex education, and wonder why this is not mandatory everywhere.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address the treatment of sex and related topics in a school setting.
Pro images might be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): We need sex education in schools.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>52</number>
<title>Should stem cell research be expanded?</title>
<description>
A user recently learned that furthering new lines of stem cell research requires the destruction of a human embryo. Shocked, the user is looking for details on the ethical issues. 
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address the use of stem cells or embryos in labs or outcomes of corresponding research.
Pro images might be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): We should expand stem cell research.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>53</number>
<title>Should blood donations be financially compensated?</title>
<description>
A user reads a report that states that hospitals need much more blood donations than are provided at the moment, and wonders why the public health system does not pay for donations.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address, for example, money and blood donations in combination or the necessity of blood donations.
Pro images might be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): We need to financially compensate blood donations.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>54</number>
<title>Should suicide be a criminal offense?</title>
<description>
A user is watching the news on TV and hears about a young adult who took their own life due to immense pressure from their environment. This case somehow sticks in the user's mind. After ruminating for days, the user feels confused and unable to say how laws should deal with suicide and whether such laws would make any difference at all.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address the topic of suicide either directly or via effects of suicides.
Pro images might be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): Suicide should be a criminal offense.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>55</number>
<title>Should agricultural subsidies be reduced?</title>
<description>
A user hears that the EU pays billions of euros in agricultural subsidies every year. The user thinks that this is too much and wonders what exactly is subsidized and by how much.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address agriculture in various forms, for example showing farmers or products. On-topic images are not necessarily referring to money, but could also, for example, show quality.
Pro images might be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): We need to reduce agricultural subsidies.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>56</number>
<title>Should vigilantism be legal?</title>
<description>
A user was following the case of a criminal in the news and was very disappointed with what he considered to be far too lenient a sentence given to the criminal. Today, the user read that the criminal was almost killed by a civilian on his way to prison. With mixed feelings, the user examines to what extent such acts of vigilante justice could be ethically justified.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address either taking justice into one's own hands or of the state's inability to provide justice (in a particular case or in general).
Pro images might be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): Vigilantism should be legal.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>57</number>
<title>Are gender or racial quotas effective?</title>
<description>
A female user recently got a job and now learns that she got the job because she was the best female applicant, even though a male applicant was rated slightly better. The user then wonders how often such quotas come into play and whether their effects are known.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address, for example, effects of either gender or racial quotas, or address implementations or statistics of such quotas.
Pro images might be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): Gender (or racial) quotas are effective.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>58</number>
<title>Should holders of public offices resign on bad approval ratings?</title>
<description>
Recently, it became known that a minister wasted billions of public money, which caused his approval ratings to plummet. Yet they do not resign and their political party does not urge them to do so. One user wonders if there should be a democratic process that allows the public to force ministers to resign.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address, for example, the performance of holders of public offices, approval ratings, or resignations.
Pro images might be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): Holders of public offices with bad approval ratings should resign.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>59</number>
<title>Should nuclear weapons be abolished?</title>
<description>
With the war in Ukraine, nuclear weapons have once again become a much-discussed topic, as they are described as both a threat and a security insurance policy. One user wonders which of the two is the stronger claim.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address nuclear weapons, for example their past usage, locations, or disarmament.
Pro images might be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): We should abolish nuclear weapons.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>60</number>
<title>Should the press be subsidized?</title>
<description>
A user is annoyed by the advertising on the website of his favorite newspaper and wonders whether it wouldn't be better to subsidize the newspapers so that they are less dependent on advertising money.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address, for example, methods of financing press or press independence.
Pro images might be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): We should subsidize the press.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>61</number>
<title>Is wind power the best alternative energy source?</title>
<description>
A user has recently heard a lot about plans in his country to invest heavily in wind energy, although solar cells have been the main topic of discussion in recent years. The user wonders if he has missed some arguments why wind energy is now preferred.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address, maybe among others, renewable sources of energy, either comparing them or expressing absolute judgements, and include wind power.
Pro images might be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): Wind power is the best alternative energy source.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>62</number>
<title>Is utilitarianism morally acceptable?</title>
<description>
A user has always been fond of the idea of utilitarianism, but has recently heard that it is a bad ideal because it discriminates against minorities. While he finds this plausible, he is also sure that utilitarianism has an answer to such accusations and would like to learn more about it.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address utilitarianism or its application in some way, for example showing numbers of positively affected people.
Pro images might be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): Utilitarianism is morally acceptable.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>63</number>
<title>Is capitalism the best form of economy?</title>
<description>
A user grew up in a capitalist society but recently became interested in communist theories. The user started to wonder how different economic systems can be compared with each other.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address, for example, money as a goal, capitalist practices, repercussions of capitalism, or ethical questions regarding capitalism.
Pro images might be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): Capitalism is the best form of economy.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>64</number>
<title>Should music that glorifies violence against women be banned?</title>
<description>
A user hears a rap song on an Internet radio station that they like very much. However, when they listen to the lyrics more closely, they realizes that the song portrays cases of domestic violence against women in a very positive light. Disgusted, the user wonders why such music is not banned.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address musicians known for lyrics that glorify violence against women, or such lyrics, or violence against women in some combination with music.
Pro images might be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): Music that glorifies violence against women should be banned.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>65</number>
<title>Should we imprison fewer people?</title>
<description>
A user hears on a TV program that the number of imprisonments in their country is increasing drastically. They wonder if this is not a good sign and what impact it would have on society if fewer people were imprisoned.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address, for example, prisons, fates of (ex-)inmates, costs and benefits of imprisonment, or processes that lead to people being imprisoned.
Pro images might be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): We should imprison fewer people.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>66</number>
<title>Is hell a real place?</title>
<description>
A user met some strangers on the street who talked to her about heaven existing. Their organization would enable the user to get there. The strangers could not convince the user, but the user begins to think about whether some people would use similar arguments to justify the existence of hell.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address, for example, depictions of hell, quotes on hell as a place, or theological inquiries.
Pro images might be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): Hell is a real place.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>67</number>
<title>Can terrorism be justified?</title>
<description>
A user was recently shocked by an act of terrorism. After a few days, however, he suddenly feels intrigued by the effectiveness of the act and wonders why his country should not pay back in kind.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address terrorism against peoples in general or with specific acts designed to induce terror in peoples.
Pro images might be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): Terrorism can be justified.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>68</number>
<title>Should celibacy be abolished?</title>
<description>
A Catholic user informs his local priest that he is getting married. The priest is very happy for the user and immediately sets out to help with the preparations. At home, the user wonders how the priest must feel since he himself is not allowed to marry or be intimate with a woman. The user then wonders why celibacy still exists.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address, for example, vows of celibacy, solitude and loneliness, or priests in love.
Pro images might be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): Celibacy should be abolished.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>69</number>
<title>Do animals have rights?</title>
<description>
A user visits the local zoo and sees that the enclosures of some animals are now construction sites as they are being expanded to meet new regulations. The user wonders how these regulations were justified.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address, for example, animals being treated in ways that would be illegal if done to humans, or comparisons of humans and animals related to ethical questions.
Pro images might be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): Animals have rights.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>70</number>
<title>Is feminism still needed?</title>
<description>
A user sees a report on the many successes of the women's movement over the last century. Impressed, they wonder if the successes have created so much momentum toward equality that activism is no longer necessary.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address the advocacy of or against women's rights, or the political, economic, personal, and social equality of the sexes.
Pro images might be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): Feminism is still needed.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>71</number>
<title>Do politicians have no right to privacy?</title>
<description>
A user in a democratic country notices how some political parties try to use a video of a leading member of the opposing party celebrating exuberantly for their own purposes. Although the user finds the party member's behavior in the video embarrassing, he wonders whether the private lives of politicians should not be better protected from politicization.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address, for example, the private lives of politicians and possibly with their disclosure.
Pro images might be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): Politicians have no right to privacy.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>72</number>
<title>Should Scotland become independent?</title>
<description>
A user travels to Scotland on vacation. In the evening, the user has several drinks with locals who complain about Scotland being part of the United Kingdom. The next day, they can't fully remember the locals' arguments and would like to hear others' opinions as well.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address, for example, the relationship of Scotland and the United Kingdom, or possibilities and challenges of an independent Scotland.
Pro images might be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): Scotland should become independent.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>73</number>
<title>Should endangered species be protected?</title>
<description>
A user is asked by activists on the street to donate to a fund for the protection of species, especially certain insects. Up to this point, the user has not cared much about insects, remembering mainly mosquitoes as members of the species. So he wonders if the world wouldn't be better without some of the species that are currently threatened.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address, for example, endangered species, survival of the fittest, species eradication, or the consequences of species extinction.
Pro images might be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): Endangered species should be protected.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>74</number>
<title>Should all museums be free of charge?</title>
<description>
A user believes that education is the key to success and should be open to everyone. Therefore, they often suggest that museums should be free of charge. However, they wonder whether this suggestion might not also have disadvantages.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address, for example, the value of museums or the cost aspect of going to a museum.
Pro images might be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): All museums should be free of charge.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>75</number>
<title>Do humans have free will?</title>
<description>
A user finds a reference in a book to the long discussion among philosophers about whether humans have free will. With a sudden interest in the subject, they decide to search for the key points of this discussion.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address, for example, scientific or theological evidence that argues for or against human free will, or with definitions of free will that suggest a straightforward answer to this question. Pro images might be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): Humans have free will.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>76</number>
<title>Are video games art?</title>
<description>
In a store, a user misinterprets a book title "Video Game Art" as suggesting that video games are art. A few hours later, the user considers that video games might actually be art themselves. He then decides to see if his reasoning is common knowledge, widely accepted, or easily attackable.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address the expression or application of human creative skill and imagination in the creation or playing of video games.
Pro images might be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): Video games are art.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>77</number>
<title>Should humans attempt to contact extra-terrestrial life?</title>
<description>
After watching a space horror movie, a user got concerned about their government's attempts to contact extra-terrestrial life.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address dangers and opportunities of contact with extra-terrestrial life.
Pro images might be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): We should attempt to contact extra-terrestrial life.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>78</number>
<title>Is psychology a science?</title>
<description>
A user was discussing with a chemist friend what it means to do science. After the discussion, the user thinks about everything again and begins to wonder whether psychology - he is thinking primarily of psychologists who study personality traits - is actually a science.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address scientific or non-scientific processes or events related to psychology.
Pro images might be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): Psychology is a science.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>79</number>
<title>Is chess a sport?</title>
<description>
A user who plays golf has seen a meme saying that golf is not a sport. He thinks this is ridiculous, since even chess is widely recognized as a sport. However, thinking about it again, he begins to wonder if chess is a sport after all.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address chess in the light of different aspects of "sport", for example effort, mastery, competition, or community.
Pro images might be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): Chess is a sport.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>80</number>
<title>Are social media platforms doing enough to prevent cyberbullying?</title>
<description>
A user finds out that strangers are spreading lies about them on social media and impersonating them on new social media platforms. They are shocked and wonder what to do and if they should contact the platforms.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address, for example, instances of cyberbullying, preventive measures and their effects, or side effects of blocking bullies.
Pro images might be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): Social media platforms do enough to prevent cyberbullying.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>81</number>
<title>Is genetically modified food unsafe?</title>
<description>
A user saw a protest against genetically modified foods on their way to the grocery store. One of the protesters told the user that the food sold at the market was dangerous because of untested genetic modifications. At home, the user wonders if the food is actually dangerous to their health.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address effects of eating genetically modified food on one's health.
Pro images might be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): Genetically modified food is unsafe.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>82</number>
<title>Does poverty cause crime?</title>
<description>
When traveling, a user often receives advice from travel guides to stay away from poor neighborhoods because the crime rate in these areas is high. After hearing this advice three times, they wonder if poverty in general causes a higher crime rate.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address the relationship of poverty of crime, for example depicting confounding variables or causal reasoning.
Pro images might be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): Poverty causes crime.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>83</number>
<title>Does legal prostitution increase human trafficking?</title>
<description>
A user hears that some people equate human trafficking and prostitution. Although the user knows the difference, they wonder about the relationship between the two, in particular whether legalizing prostitution would lead to an increase in (still illegal) human trafficking.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address, for example, causes of human trafficking, and specifically the relationship of prostitution and human trafficking.
Pro images might be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): Legal prostitution increases human trafficking.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>84</number>
<title>Is the earth flat?</title>
<description>
A user was told by a friend that there is new evidence that the Earth is flat. While the user is pretty sure that the friend is making fun of him, he is not entirely sure. Therefore, he decides to look for the new evidence.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address, for examples, experiment descriptions or observations that (falsely) indicate a flat or a non-flat earth.
Pro images might be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): The earth is flat.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>85</number>
<title>Should human cloning be banned?</title>
<description>
 A user saw a sci-fi movie in which teleportation was performed by scanning people, sending the scanned data over the Internet, reproducing the person at the destination using the scanned data, and finally killing the original person. The user thinks this type of teleportation is wrong, but can't put their finger on what exactly they think is wrong. To get to the bottom of the matter, the user decides to first look into the pros and cons of human cloning. 
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address various issues or benefits of human cloning, for example of ethical nature.
Pro images might be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): Human cloning should be banned.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>86</number>
<title>Is communism better than democracy?</title>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>87</number>
<title>Are gas prices too high?</title>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>88</number>
<title>Should Turkey join the EU?</title>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>89</number>
<title>Should hate speech be penalized more?</title>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>90</number>
<title>Was the Iraq war legal?</title>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>91</number>
<title>Should bullfighting be banned?</title>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>92</number>
<title>Should the UNO become a world government?</title>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>93</number>
<title>How should nuclear waste be stored?</title>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>94</number>
<title>Should children have mobile phones?</title>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>95</number>
<title>Should the inheritance tax be raised?</title>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>96</number>
<title>Should government spending be reduced?</title>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>97</number>
<title>Should children beauty contests be banned?</title>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>98</number>
<title>Should the US Electoral college be abolished?</title>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>99</number>
<title>Should social networks be banned?</title>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>100</number>
<title>Do we need cash?</title>
</topic>

</topics>
