<topics>
	
<topic>
<number>51</number>
<title>Do we need sex education in schools?</title>
<description>
An adult user now has a partner for the first time and searched the Internet for information on contraception. They found that some schools provide sex education, and wonder why this is not mandatory everywhere.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address the treatment of sex and related topics in a school setting.
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): We need sex education in schools.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>52</number>
<title>Should stem cell research be expanded?</title>
<description>
A user recently learned that furthering new lines of stem cell research requires the destruction of a human embryo. Shocked, the user is looking for details on the ethical issues. 
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address the use of stem cells or embryos in labs or outcomes of corresponding research.
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): We should expand stem cell research.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>53</number>
<title>Should blood donations be financially compensated?</title>
<description>
A user reads a report that states that hospitals need much more blood donations than are provided at the moment, and wonders why the public health system does not pay for donations.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address, for example, money and blood donations in combination or the necessity of blood donations.
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): We need to financially compensate blood donations.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>54</number>
<title>Should suicide be a criminal offense?</title>
<description>
A user is watching the news on TV and hears about a young adult who took their own life due to immense pressure from their environment. This case somehow sticks in the user's mind. After ruminating for days, the user feels confused and unable to say how laws should deal with suicide and whether such laws would make any difference at all.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address the topic of suicide either directly or via effects of suicides.
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): Suicide should be a criminal offense.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>55</number>
<title>Should agricultural subsidies be reduced?</title>
<description>
A user hears that the EU pays billions of euros in agricultural subsidies every year. The user thinks that this is too much and wonders what exactly is subsidized and by how much.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address agriculture in various forms, for example showing farmers or products. On-topic images are not necessarily referring to money, but could also, for example, show quality.
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): We need to reduce agricultural subsidies.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>56</number>
<title>Should vigilantism be legal?</title>
<description>
A user was following the case of a criminal in the news and was very disappointed with what he considered to be far too lenient a sentence given to the criminal. Today, the user read that the criminal was almost killed by a civilian on his way to prison. With mixed feelings, the user examines to what extent such acts of vigilante justice could be ethically justified.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address either taking justice into one's own hands or of the state's inability to provide justice (in a particular case or in general).
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): Vigilantism should be legal.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>57</number>
<title>Are gender or racial quotas effective?</title>
<description>
A female user recently got a job and now learns that she got the job because she was the best female applicant, even though a male applicant was rated slightly better. The user then wonders how often such quotas come into play and whether their effects are known.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address, for example, effects of either gender or racial quotas, or address implementations or statistics of such quotas.
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): Gender (or racial) quotas are effective.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>58</number>
<title>Should holders of public offices resign on bad approval ratings?</title>
<description>
Recently, it became known that a minister wasted billions of public money, which caused his approval ratings to plummet. Yet they do not resign and their political party does not urge them to do so. One user wonders if there should be a democratic process that allows the public to force ministers to resign.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address, for example, the performance of holders of public offices, approval ratings, or resignations.
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): Holders of public offices with bad approval ratings should resign.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>59</number>
<title>Should nuclear weapons be abolished?</title>
<description>
With the war in Ukraine, nuclear weapons have once again become a much-discussed topic, as they are described as both a threat and a security insurance policy. One user wonders which of the two is the stronger claim.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address nuclear weapons, for example their past usage, locations, or disarmament.
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): We should abolish nuclear weapons.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>60</number>
<title>Should the press be subsidized?</title>
<description>
A user is annoyed by the advertising on the website of his favorite newspaper and wonders whether it wouldn't be better to subsidize the newspapers so that they are less dependent on advertising money.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address, for example, methods of financing press or press independence.
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): We should subsidize the press.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>61</number>
<title>Is wind power the best alternative energy source?</title>
<description>
A user has recently heard a lot about plans in his country to invest heavily in wind energy, although solar cells have been the main topic of discussion in recent years. The user wonders if he has missed some arguments why wind energy is now preferred.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address, maybe among others, renewable sources of energy, either comparing them or expressing absolute judgements, and include wind power.
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): Wind power is the best alternative energy source.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>62</number>
<title>Is utilitarianism morally acceptable?</title>
<description>
A user has always been fond of the idea of utilitarianism, but has recently heard that it is a bad ideal because it discriminates against minorities. While he finds this plausible, he is also sure that utilitarianism has an answer to such accusations and would like to learn more about it.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address utilitarianism or its application in some way, for example showing numbers of positively affected people.
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): Utilitarianism is morally acceptable.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>63</number>
<title>Is capitalism the best form of economy?</title>
<description>
A user grew up in a capitalist society but recently became interested in communist theories. The user started to wonder how different economic systems can be compared with each other.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address, for example, money as a goal, capitalist practices, repercussions of capitalism, or ethical questions regarding capitalism.
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): Capitalism is the best form of economy.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>64</number>
<title>Should music that glorifies violence against women be banned?</title>
<description>
A user hears a rap song on an Internet radio station that they like very much. However, when they listen to the lyrics more closely, they realizes that the song portrays cases of domestic violence against women in a very positive light. Disgusted, the user wonders why such music is not banned.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address musicians known for lyrics that glorify violence against women, or such lyrics, or violence against women in some combination with music.
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): Music that glorifies violence against women should be banned.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>65</number>
<title>Should we imprison fewer people?</title>
<description>
A user hears on a TV program that the number of imprisonments in their country is increasing drastically. They wonder if this is not a good sign and what impact it would have on society if fewer people were imprisoned.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address, for example, prisons, fates of (ex-)inmates, costs and benefits of imprisonment, or processes that lead to people being imprisoned.
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): We should imprison fewer people.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>66</number>
<title>Is hell a real place?</title>
<description>
A user met some strangers on the street who talked to her about heaven existing. Their organization would enable the user to get there. The strangers could not convince the user, but the user begins to think about whether some people would use similar arguments to justify the existence of hell.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address, for example, depictions of hell, quotes on hell as a place, or theological inquiries.
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): Hell is a real place.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>67</number>
<title>Can terrorism be justified?</title>
<description>
A user was recently shocked by an act of terrorism. After a few days, however, he suddenly feels intrigued by the effectiveness of the act and wonders why his country should not pay back in kind.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address terrorism against peoples in general or with specific acts designed to induce terror in peoples.
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): Terrorism can be justified.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>68</number>
<title>Should celibacy be abolished?</title>
<description>
A Catholic user informs his local priest that he is getting married. The priest is very happy for the user and immediately sets out to help with the preparations. At home, the user wonders how the priest must feel since he himself is not allowed to marry or be intimate with a woman. The user then wonders why celibacy still exists.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address, for example, vows of celibacy, solitude and loneliness, or priests in love.
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): Celibacy should be abolished.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>69</number>
<title>Do animals have rights?</title>
<description>
 A user visits the local zoo and sees that the enclosures of some animals are now construction sites as they are being expanded to meet new regulations. The user wonders how these regulations were justified.
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address, for example, animals being treated in ways that would be illegal if done to humans, or comparisons of humans and animals related to ethical questions.
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): Animals have rights.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>70</number>
<title>Is feminism still needed?</title>
<description>
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): 
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>71</number>
<title>Do politicians have no right to privacy?</title>
<description>
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): 
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>72</number>
<title>Should Scotland become independent?</title>
<description>
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): 
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>73</number>
<title>Should endangered species be protected?</title>
<description>
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): 
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>74</number>
<title>Should all museums be free of charge?</title>
<description>
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): 
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>75</number>
<title>Do humans have free will?</title>
<description>
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): 
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>76</number>
<title>Are video games art?</title>
<description>
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): 
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>77</number>
<title>Should humans attempt to contact extra-terrestrial life?</title>
<description>
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): 
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>78</number>
<title>Is psychology a science?</title>
<description>
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): 
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>79</number>
<title>Is chess a sport?</title>
<description>
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): 
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>80</number>
<title>How can we combat cyberbullying?</title>
<description>
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): 
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>81</number>
<title>Is genetically modified food unsafe?</title>
<description>
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): 
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>82</number>
<title>Does poverty cause crime?</title>
<description>
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): 
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>83</number>
<title>Should prostitution be legalized?</title>
<description>
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): 
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>84</number>
<title>Is the earth flat?</title>
<description>
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): 
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>85</number>
<title>Should human cloning be banned?</title>
<description>
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): 
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>86</number>
<title>Is communism better than democracy?</title>
<description>
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): 
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>87</number>
<title>Are gas prices too high?</title>
<description>
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): 
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>88</number>
<title>Should Turkey join the EU?</title>
<description>
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): 
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>89</number>
<title>Should hate speech be penalized more?</title>
<description>
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): 
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>90</number>
<title>Was the Iraq war legal?</title>
<description>
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): 
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>91</number>
<title>Should bullfighting be banned?</title>
<description>
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): 
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>92</number>
<title>Should the UNO become a world government?</title>
<description>
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): 
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>93</number>
<title>How should nuclear waste be stored?</title>
<description>
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): 
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>94</number>
<title>Should children have mobile phones?</title>
<description>
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): 
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>95</number>
<title>Should the inheritance tax be raised?</title>
<description>
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): 
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>96</number>
<title>Should government spending be reduced?</title>
<description>
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): 
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>97</number>
<title>Should children beauty contests be banned?</title>
<description>
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): 
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>98</number>
<title>Should the US Electoral college be abolished?</title>
<description>
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): 
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>99</number>
<title>Should social networks be banned?</title>
<description>
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): 
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>100</number>
<title>Do we need cash?</title>
<description>
</description>
<narrative>
On-topic images address
Pro images could be shared on social media with this text (no irony, no link): 
</narrative>
</topic>

</topics>
